<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ethereum Developer Curriculum</title><link>https://EthBuilders.github.io/Curriculum/</link><description>Recent content on Ethereum Developer Curriculum</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 18:21:09 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://EthBuilders.github.io/Curriculum/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Basics</title><link>https://EthBuilders.github.io/Curriculum/basics/git/basics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 00:29:07 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://EthBuilders.github.io/Curriculum/basics/git/basics/</guid><description>The Basics When starting out with git, there really is only a few commands you need to know. For the purposes of this mini-tutorial I&amp;rsquo;m assuming you have a basic understanding of how to use a shell. I highly recommend you take a brief moment to refresh yourself, or do some mini-practice (Cheat Sheet).
The nine basic commands you&amp;rsquo;ll need to know are:
git config A convenience function that is used to set Git configuration values on a global or local project level git clone Clones a repository into a newly created directory git checkout Updates files in the working tree to match the version in the index or the specified tree Don&amp;rsquo;t worry too much about knowing what the working tree, index, or staging are just yet, although you&amp;rsquo;re more than welcome to take a deep dive git status Displays paths that have differences between the index file and the current HEAD commit git add This command updates the index using the current content found in the working tree git commit Create a new commit containing the current contents of the index and the given log message describing the changes git merge Incorporates changes from the named commits (since the time their histories diverged from the current branch) into the current branch git pull Incorporates changes from a remote repository into the current branch git push Updates remote refs using local refs, while sending objects necessary to complete the given refs.</description></item><item><title>Open Source Collaboration</title><link>https://EthBuilders.github.io/Curriculum/basics/open_source/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 00:23:45 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://EthBuilders.github.io/Curriculum/basics/open_source/</guid><description>Before learning about the tools used for Open Source Collaboration, it&amp;rsquo;s best you get an idea of why they exist in the first place, and what exactly open source means. The best place to start when learning about Open Source ofcourse would be the source, pun possibly intended. The Open Source Initiative (a.k.a OSI) is a non-profit corporation which is mission-bound to educate, advocate for, and build bridges within the open source community.</description></item><item><title>Design Patterns</title><link>https://EthBuilders.github.io/Curriculum/basics/design_patterns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 00:52:03 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://EthBuilders.github.io/Curriculum/basics/design_patterns/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://EthBuilders.github.io/Curriculum/basics/support/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://EthBuilders.github.io/Curriculum/basics/support/</guid><description>EthBuilders Curriculum Support Table of Contents EthBuilders Curriculum Support Table of Contents Project Contact Info Anthony A (Organizer | Developer) Edward Amor (Developer) Common Commands Bash Terminal Show Directory Information Navigate Directories Manipulate Files Display Files Git Git Information Make Changes Commit Changes Update the Repo Delete Branch Yarn | NPM Set Up Instructions macOS and Linux Setup Windows Setup Accesssing Command Line Via macOS Via Windows General Resources and Links Git / Github Project Contact Info Join our Slack</description></item></channel></rss>